CHRISTOPHER KSIAZAK

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Summary

I'm a developer born and raised in El Paso, TX. I enjoy learning new technologies and applying that knowledge in designing and creating things that live on the web. For over a year, I attended Lambda School for Full Stack Web Development, part-time, all while working user analytics and support, where I worked with various distributed teams ranging from data science, to UX designers, to other developers, creating and iterating on products. Afterwards, I started working with E-Dealer Direct, which was cut short due to COVID. Within a few weeks, I connected with Ariana Suisse SA and was offered the opportunity of implementing a distributed service system. After a few months, I was offered my position back at E-Dealer Direct, which through proper time management, I was able to complete both tasks as needed and without delay.

Before I started engineering. I assisted in identifying ways that we could improve product and issue resolution time to deliver better customer support to both end users and clients, as well as quantifying user impact on issues.

Employment

E-Dealer Direct Software Engineer

El Paso, TX July 2020 to Current

As life semi-returns to normal due to the current COVID-19 situation, I was asked to return to my position at E-Dealer Direct. In my current role, I operate both across the full stack and mobile development. My typical day to day technologies in use are React, React Native, Redux, SCSS, And Ruby on Rails. I lead product team discussions, and push out updates in a regular and timely manner, while both taking feedback on the current release and working on the next.

Ariana Suisse SA Software Engineer (Contract)

Remote May 2020 to Feb. 2021

In my partnership with Ariana Suisse, I was the lead developer on creating a multitenant, distributed system using React (& React Native), GraphQL, Apollo Federation, Styled Components, Typescript, Elasticsearch, and integrated various AWS services. Through discussions with clients, I continually created new features or reiterated on old ones. This was done remotely across global time zones.

E-Dealer Direct Software Engineer

El Paso, TX Mar. 2020 to Apr. 2020

Although not long, I joined E-Dealer Direct and served as part of the core engineering team. In my time there, I contributed to stack discussions in an agile environment, created wireframes and mockups using Figma, and planned and developed new features using React, Redux, SCSS, Javascript, and Ruby on Rails. Unfortunately, due to COVID-19, my time was cut short.

C3i Solutions Project Coordinator

El Paso, TX Mar. 2017 to Current

At C3i Solutions, I worked in conjunction with our client, Castlight Health, and assisted transitioning our support program through several of our client's product launches. I maintained our support knowledge base, quantified user issues and triaged bug reports to appropriate engineering teams, through which I made data driven decisions through various reports from Salesforce and JIRA. On top of that, I regularly analyzed flat files and API requests from Anthem.

Contact

- cksiazak@gmail.com
- ksiazak.dev
- **(915) 253-8705**
- **♥** El Paso. Texas
- cksiazak_dev
- in cksiazak
- C) cksiazak

Education

Lambda School Apr. 2019 to June 2020

Skills

WEB DEVELOPMENT

CSS (LESS/SASS)

Javascript/Typescript

React

Redux

Node

SOL

Ruby on Rails

GraphOL

React Native

REPORTING, DOCUMENTATION, AND ANALYTICS

JIRA

Tableau

Confluence

Datadog

Salesforce